[{"stepName": "Identify Motion of objects", "stepNumber": 1, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "How many moving objects are present?", "options": [2, 3, 4, 1], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 0, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": "", "show2": "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084", "showfc": []}, {"question": "How many strings are there?", "options": [4, 3, 0, 2], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "motion", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 0, "tobeshown": 1, "show1": "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084", "show": "Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "showfc": []}]}, {"stepName": "Write FBD equation for each Moving block", "stepNumber": 2, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 downwards", "T\u2081 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 downwards", "T\u2082 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of second pulley in the y-direction", "options": ["+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for second pulley cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 3}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 down the incline ", "T\u2081 up the incline "], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 up the incline ", "T\u2081 down the incline "], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 up the incline ", "T\u2082 down the incline "], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of second pulley in the y-direction", "options": ["+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Understanding", "stepNumber": 3, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for red block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on red block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 downwards", "T\u2081 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of red block in the y-direction", "options": ["+30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "-30+T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, "], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Red block", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: 30", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for yellow block cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on yellow block?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 downwards", "T\u2082 upwards"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of yellow block in the y-direction", "options": ["+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082+40=4.0a\u2082", "-T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Yellow block", "Upward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Downward Forces: 40", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of second pulley in the y-direction", "options": ["+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "At how many points does the imaginary sphere for second pulley cuts the strings", "options": [0, 1, 2, 3], "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": -100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "answer": 3}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 down the incline ", "T\u2081 up the incline "], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2081 up the incline ", "T\u2081 down the incline "], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "What is the force at this point of intersection on second pulley?", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["T\u2082 up the incline ", "T\u2082 down the incline "], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 3, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "]}, {"question": "Whats the FBD equation of second pulley in the y-direction", "options": ["+2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "-2T\u2081+T\u2082=0.0", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "answer": 3, "threejsstep": "fbd", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 100, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082"], "tobeshown": 0, "showfc": ["Second pulley", "Upward Forces: T\u2081, T\u2081, ", "Downward Forces: T\u2082, ", "Rightward Forces: ", "Leftward Forces: "], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"]}]}, {"stepName": "Constraint Equations", "stepNumber": 4, "stepQuestions": [{"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081+2.0a\u2084=0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2081+2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is the number of parts which change length in the pink string?", "options": [6, 5, 3, 4], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": -1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2081", "-a\u2081"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2082 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2084", "-a\u2084"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2083 for pink string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2084", "-a\u2084"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 3, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for pink string?", "options": ["+a\u2081+2.0a\u2084=0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2081+2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 1, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2084=0"], "tobeshown": 0}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2084=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2084=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2084=0"], "tobeshown": 1}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2084", "-a\u2084"], "answer": 0, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 1, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"]}, {"question": "What is double derivative of change in l\u2081 for red string:", "tobeshown": 0, "options": ["+a\u2082", "-a\u2082"], "answer": 1, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 4, "threejssubsubstep": 2, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"]}, {"question": "What is the constraint equation for red string?", "options": ["+a\u2082+a\u2084=0", "+a\u2082-a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082-a\u2084=0"], "answer": 2, "threejsstep": "constraint", "threejssubstep": 2, "threejssubsubstep": 300, "show1": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0"], "show2": ["Unknowns: a\u2081, a\u2082, a\u2084, T\u2081, T\u2082, ", "+30-T\u2081=3.0a\u2081", "+T\u2082-40=4.0a\u2082", "+2T\u2081-T\u2082=0.0", "+a\u2081-2.0a\u2084=0", "-a\u2082+a\u2084=0"], "tobeshown": 0}]}]